Guide to the Edwin R. Hoskins papers, [ca.1911-1962].
Hoskins, Edwin R. papers,
- Section XYZ-II: Adult Education, 1935-1953
  - Hoskins' associations with the N.Y. State Citizens' Council and the American Association of Adult Education: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    Re: 1946 N.Y. State Institute of Community Leadership
  - Hoskins' associations with the N.Y. State Citizens' Council and the American Association of Adult Education: Correspondence, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    Re: Leadership Workshop
  - American Association of Adult Education and miscellaneous conference information, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    Information re: American Association of Adult Education, Berkeley, California, 1939 (Pacific Southwest Conference). Miscellaneous questionnaires and information on other conferences
  - N.Y. State Programs in Schools, 1949-1953 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - N.Y. State Programs in Schools, 1949-1953 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Student Report: Rural Education Course #134A, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Student Report: Adult Education in Dallas, Texas, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Bulletins, 1930-1950 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Bulletins, 1930-1950 (Box 3, Folder 101)